Saeed Mardomi

.NET Developer

Experienced Dotnet Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the Computer Software industry. Strong engineering professional skilled in .Net and familiar with Microservice architecture , CQRS pattern and gRPC.

Tabriz, East Azerbaijan Province, Iran (Birthdate: 1995/03/09)

saeedmardomi@hotmail.com (+98 914 732 00 63)



Skills

- .NET Core
- EF Core
- OOP
- Microservices
- Redis
- MongoDB
- CQRS
- gRPC
- REST API
- Dapper
- PLSQL
- TSQI
- Git / TFS
- Clean Code
- Scrum

Languages

- English Intermediate
- Azerbaijani Native or Bilingual
- Turkish Fluent

Work Experience



.Net Developer • Manir

April 2019 - August 2022

I was a member of a team of 6 people working on the integrated service system of electricity subscribers with Scrum methodology.

The technologies used are:

Asp.Net Core

Oracle Database

Dapper

Typescript

Auto Mapper



Remote .NET Developer • EPEVER

May 2018 - September 2020

I was working remotely and as a project.

The worked projects included Learning management system and company's blog.

The technologies used are:

Asp.net MVC

SQL Server

EntityFramework Code First

Html

Css

Bootstrap

Jquery



Virtual training expert, Developer • Tahlilgaran

May 2016 - March 2018

Production of electronic content in the form of designing 2D educational games with Action Script .

Education



Bachelor's degree, Information Technology

2014 - 2018

Powered by CakeResume